Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
(sentimental music)
- [Ethan] They say when you die.
your life flashes
before your eyes.
The people you loved...
The good moments...
And the bad...
- [Emma] I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- [Ethan] My memories
are a confusing blur.
Maybe it's for the best.
Because right now. my life is
something I'd rather forget.
(sentimental music)
(gunshot booming)
(crickets chirping)
(ominous music)
- [TV Announcer] As
cases surge globally
more than tripling
in the last week.
most governments have issued
shelter in place orders
for all non-essential workers.
Despite ongoing uncertainty
as to the virus' source.
the scientific community
agrees. the transmission occurs-
- [Emma] Hey. you all right?
(alarm blaring)
- Jesus Christ.
- Another alert.
Nearby.
- [Ethan] We left too late.
- [TV Announcer] The three
early warning signs of infection
are severe headaches-
- [Emma] Ethan. I can drive.
(mysterious music)
- Hello?
(Emma screaming)
(mysterious music)
Emma!
Where is everyone?
Hello!
(mysterious music)
Emma!
Hello!
(mysterious music)
(mysterious music continues)
(tires screeching)
Hey. hey!
- You lost?
- Yeah. I just woke up. I
don't know where the fuck I am.
(tense music)
(bullets crackling)
- Come on. get out here!
(gunshots booming)
(tense music)
(mystifying music)
- Okay.
- [Mae] Shit.
You blind bitch.
- I don't even know these guys.
I'm just looking
for my girlfriend.
- Stop staring. it's rude.
You shouldn't be out here alone.
- [Ethan] You are.
- Yeah. Well. I'm not an idiot.
Okay.
- I was in a car
accident. I was with Emma.
we were driving to the lake.
(console beeping)
- Yes!
- Where are we?
- Gimme a hand.
- What if he wakes up?
- Happy?
You okay?
- Yeah. yeah. I just...
(body thudding)
(enigmatic music)
(soft music)
(shrill music)
(curios music)
- [Mae] Look who
finally woke up.
How's your head?
- I'm...
- I'm Mae.
- I'm Ethan.
- You sure?
- I've got amnesia.
- No shit.
I left some clothes for
you on top of the dresser.
You must have missed them.
Unless this is a style choice.
- I'll be right back.
(curious music)
- Ooh. looking good.
- It smells delicious.
- It's not ready.
do not touch it.
My generator.
- Kinetic energy.
- Clever boy.
So what do you remember?
(cryptic music)
- [Ethan] My girlfriend
and I gathered our supplies
and headed to our cabin.
We were gonna wait it out there.
It's isolated. safe.
And hopefully she's
there waiting for me.
(cryptic music)
- A piece of advice. keep
your amnesia to yourself.
People today are looking
for weaknesses in others.
- What happened?
- [Mae] Well. we've
been threatening
to let viruses wipe
us out for years.
One finally called our bluff.
Some say it's the planet's
attempt to reclaim balance
by killing us all off.
- [Ethan] In days?
How is that possible?
- Nature's a powerful bitch.
Fuck!
I'll be right back.
Don't touch anything.
- [Ethan] Mae?
I should probably head out.
(piano key playing)
- Hey!
What did I say?
Don't touch anything!
- Who are you?
(foreboding music)
Mae?
Mae. there's something
or someone over there.
- That's Myrtle. she's fine.
just don't get too close.
- Shouldn't we-
- I said she's fine.
Live and let live.
(foreboding music)
Geez.
- Can I help?
- You an expert with generators?
- Actually. I think I am.
- Have at it.
Well. what do you think?
- [Ethan] First of all. whoever
set this up is an idiot.
No offense.
- None taken.
Way to go!
Hey. hey. hey.
That ego of yours is
going to your head.
Okay. come on. let's
move it and shake it.
- Mae. I wasn't kidding. I
need to go and find Emma.
(enigmatic music)
(Mae chuckling)
- We're gonna to
eat good tonight.
- Is that a possum?
Are you alone out here?
- Most days.
- You have a husband?
- You got a point?
- Oh. just wondering if
it's safe out here alone.
- I'm not alone. I got Myrtle.
(enigmatic music)
Don't worry. I'm
not gonna kill you.
- I know.
- [Mae] Besides. look at me.
you could beat me
to death with ease.
- I don't want that.
- But do not go snooping around.
unless you have a
death wish. okay?
Because every room in
here is booby-trapped.
I mean it.
- Define booby-
(gun clicking)
Jesus!
What are you doing?
- Shoot me.
- No.
- Good boy.
You see that?
Red means dead.
If you pulled that trigger.
I'd be dead right now.
Hungry?
(enigmatic music)
- [Ethan] That was really good.
It's getting kind of
late. I should probably-
- [Mae] Ethan. you know.
I hate to ask you this.
but I could just
really use your help.
- With what?
♪ Ah ♪
♪ And I don't hardly know her ♪
♪ But think I could love her ♪
♪ Crimson and clover ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ When she come walking over ♪
♪ Now I've been
waitin' to show her ♪
You gotta be kidding me.
♪ Crimson and clover ♪
♪ Over and over ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ My. my such a sweet thing ♪
♪ I wanna do everything ♪
♪ What a beautiful feeling ♪
♪ Crimson and clover ♪
♪ Over and over ♪
Mae. it's late. I
should hit the road.
- [Mae] Really?
You're gonna let an old
lady dance all by herself?
♪ Crimson and clover
over and over ♪
- Listen. Mae. I
should probably-
- You play cards?
(gentle piano music)
- Two of hearts.
No. thanks. I'm good.
- Harder to kill
when you're sober.
That's okay.
I love a challenge.
- Maybe you've had enough.
- Bullshit.
(Mae laughing)
Gotcha.
- I used to be
good at this game.
- [Mae] Yeah. well.
you're a terrible liar.
Your face. no secrets.
- Yeah?
What about your face?
Sorry. I didn't mean to.
- Yeah.
It's getting late.
- Mae. I appreciate you
taking me in. feeding me.
but I promised Emma-
- Nothing good happens
after dark. Ethan.
- I promised Emma.
I would protect her.
- Have a good night's sleep.
We'll find her tomorrow.
Trust me. Myrtle is the least
of your worries out there.
This is where you say thank you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Good night.
Go to bed.
(uneasy music)
- Say it back.
If we ever get separated. meet
at the cabin. Candle Lake.
- [Emma] Got it.
(uneasy music)
(tires screeching)
- Wake up.
(menacing music)
- Emma.
Emma!
(glass shattering)
(menacing music)
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
- [Jolene] Drop it.
(crowbar thudding)
Sam.
Stay there. honey.
- I don't want any trouble.
I'm just looking
for my girlfriend.
- [Jolene] Emma?
- Yes.
Have you seen her?
- No.
You are out there yelling
her name like an idiot.
(footsteps thudding)
(menacing music)
(creature growling)
(Jolene screaming)
(flesh squelching)
(menacing music)
(Jolene screaming)
(gun clicking)
(flesh squelching)
Okay.
Eyes closed.
Yeah?
(thunder crackling)
- [Ethan] How is it still alive?
I bashed its skull in.
- Alive.
That's generous.
Out here. most are
pretty far gone.
more plant than people now.
so yeah. head kills
don't really work.
If I had any bullets.
you'd already be dead.
- Oh. appreciate the honesty.
What do they want?
- [Jolene] Same as
any of us. I guess.
Food.
Mostly food.
I'm Jolene.
That's my son. Sam.
- Ethan.
- Where'd you get a cast?
- I was in an accident
and my girlfriend Emma.
she's a doctor.
- A doctor.
That's lucky.
When's the last
time you saw her?
- [Ethan] A few days.
- [Jolene] I hate
to break it to you.
but we have been here for weeks
and I haven't seen anyone.
except the plant parade.
- She'll be here.
This is our spot.
- Yeah. don't be so sure.
It's just...
Hope is dangerous.
He thinks his dad
is coming back.
- What happened to him?
- [Jolene] The same thing
that happened to everyone.
I made a choice.
(calm music)
Distract me. Ethan.
tell me something good.
- Like what?
- You and Emma.
(loving music)
- [Ethan] This may sound weird.
and I know it's not true.
but I feel like I've
known her my whole life.
When I close my eyes
and I think of her.
it's not the big
moments that stand out.
it's the dumb little things.
I think of how we take care of
each other. amuse each other.
even in the bad times.
Unfortunately. in our
dumpster fire of a world.
the bad times started
to overshadow the good.
Wherever you turned.
people were at their worst.
violent. cruel. fed up.
(dire music)
Honestly. when I heard
the virus was plant-based.
I wasn't surprised.
It's like the planet finally
had enough of our shit.
Hey.
- [News Anchor] After
the deadliest day yet.
social media is dubbing the
infected. "The Reclaimed"
based on a popular
conspiracy theory
that nature is purging itself
from mankind's destruction.
Disturbing visuals are going
viral at an alarming rate.
- [Ethan] Is she okay?
Shit. that looks bad.
- [Reporter] Excuse me.
(woman growling)
- [Emma] Whatever this is.
it's not turning around.
We need to get the
hell outta here.
- [Ethan] Tonight.
- [Emma] Tonight.
- [Ethan] We got out.
I remember that much.
- [Jolene] Ethan.
Ethan.
- Yeah?
- You can sleep.
- I'm good.
- [Jolene] Honestly. I'll
take the first watch.
I'm not even tired.
Ethan.
- Yeah.
- If you mess with me or
my kid. I'll kill you.
(thunder rumbling)
Okay?
(heart monitor beeping)
(Emma giggling)
- Ethan. what's wrong?
(creature growling)
If anything goes sideways.
meet at the cabin.
(spine-tingling music)
Wake up.
(scary music)
- Ethan!
(scary music continues)
(creature growling)
(scary music)
(emotional music)
- Hey. just try to relax.
- Was that a person?
- Used to be.
(gunshots booming)
- Was that necessary?
- Yeah. actually.
These things are unstoppable.
I just bought us some time.
Stay here.
(bullets booming)
(odd music)
Find what you're looking for?
My name is Mae by the way.
- Hi. baby.
If you're watching this.
I'm guessing we're apart.
You're probably confused.
Well. more so than usual.
Your amnesia. your
amnesia is getting worse.
Erratic.
I keep losing you.
I mean. I don't know
if I can keep this up.
(melancholy music)
The world isn't
what it used to be.
People are changing
for the worst.
I guess what I'm saying
is if you're lost
and I'm not with you-
- [Ethan] No. no. no!
- Hey. hey!
Don't do that!
You will draw them
out. I'm serious.
I'm serious.
I have a charger
back at my place.
It's okay. come on. let's go.
- Wow. nice truck.
- Well. it would be
if some idiot hadn't
drained the battery.
- What?
- I'm gonna wipe your face.
- Sorry I was weird back there.
I have amnesia.
- Yeah. I know.
We've done this before.
- We have?
- How are you feeling?
- My head is swimming.
I'm Ethan. by the way.
- Mae. like I said.
Well. let's charge that
phone of yours. shall we?
Oh. shit.
Fuck!
- Can you get another pair?
- Do you know how many
people I had to kill
for that prescription?
Hop on.
- Hop on?
- Get on the back of the bike.
Let's go.
Come on.
Steady right there.
Okay. put your feet up.
- [Ethan] Okay.
- [Mae] Lift your feet up.
- [Ethan] They're
up. they're up.
(tender music)
How far is your house?
- Far enough.
- You wanna switch?
- You're dreaming if I think
I'm gonna let you drive.
(tender music)
My feet are killing me.
I hope this stupid girl
of yours is worth it.
- She is.
(Mae chuckling)
What's so funny?
- I don't know. you
just seem so fired up.
- I am.
I'm not stopping
until I find her.
Don't you have anyone?
- Sort of.
He died.
- I'm sorry.
- No. you're not.
- What's your story?
- What's my story?
Are you serious?
Do you really care or are
you just making small talk?
- I need a distraction
from my thoughts. I guess.
- At least you're honest.
My story.
I don't know.
I live alone.
I have a great garden.
I hunt and I take in strangers.
- Tell me something
personal. something real.
- I'm lonely and kind
of wish I was dead.
- That's a-
- An overshare?
- An overshare.
- [Mae] You asked me.
(inquisitive music)
You okay?
- [Announcer] This
is not a test.
This is the emergency
alert system
reporting a mandatory
evacuation order
for all local residents.
Gather food. water.
and medical supplies.
- [Mae] Okay. 30 seconds tops.
This place looks sketchy.
- Well?
- [Mae] What do you think?
Admit it. we're fucked.
- We'll be okay.
I'll protect us.
- More like the
other way around.
(frightening music)
- Emma!
(gunshot booming)
- You actually did it!
- Don't sound so surprised.
- You okay?
My name is Mae.
- I know.
I must have tripped is all.
- [Mae] No. you passed
out. that's what happened.
Are you sure you're okay?
- I'm fine.
I'm just hungry. I think.
(peaceful music)
- Finally.
(inauspicious music)
- [Ethan] What?
- Hey!
We're armed.
Get out or I will shoot you!
- Wait. wait. wait. wait. wait!
Please. I rather you didn't.
I just. I saw your
house. you had power.
I just. I figured-
- You'd break in.
- [Tom] No. I knocked.
But you know how it is. it
could have been abandoned.
I'm Tom.
And you are?
- Skeptical.
- [Tom] That's fair.
'Sup?
- You alone?
- I lost my wife. like
somewhere in the area
and I'm just. I'm looking
for her. you know?
- You got a gun?
- No.
- Out here you don't have a
gun. are you fucking stupid?
- Come on. lady. now
you're just being mean.
I have one gun.
Just one.
- Just one?
- That's it.
I promise.
- Pat him down.
- You wanna tell your
mom to chill out?
- She's not my mom.
- Look. I didn't come here
for any trouble. all right?
I'm just. I'm
looking for answers.
And honestly. any
food you could spare.
I mean. you know how tough
it is out here. right?
Or maybe you don't.
I mean. you have kale.
- You know. Tom.
trust is earned.
One hot meal in
exchange for one chore.
You got it?
- Yeah.
Define chore.
- Well. I hate to
ask. but it's rare
that I have two strong
men at my disposal.
There's a few things
I can't do by myself.
- I'm yours.
Hey. did you also think she
was gonna ask for a three-way?
- What?
No.
- I'm just kidding.
How do you two know each other?
- I lost someone too.
She's helping me find her.
- Sorry to hear.
(Emma screaming)
You all right?
I'm gonna go take a leak.
I'll be back in one second.
- Hey. boys.
- Wow. lemonade.
- [Mae] Fresh lemons.
- Anything else in here?
- Just poison.
Who's hungry?
- Hey. do you have
anywhere I can wash up?
- Yeah. there's a
sink right here.
Help yourself.
- [Tom] Thank you.
It smells great.
- Thank you.
Say you're not hungry.
- I'm starving. I can
barely see straight.
- Say you're not hungry.
I'll cook for you later.
- Mae.
- Do what I fucking say.
Let's eat.
(mellow piano music)
- God damn. Mae. I haven't
eaten like this in years.
- You're welcome.
(stomach grumbling)
Wow.
Hello.
Is that your stomach?
Are you sure you don't want any?
- I'm good.
I'm just not hungry.
- Why don't we finish
this bottle of wine off?
What do you think?
- [Tom] Me and you?
Who am I to say no?
(Tom chuckling)
- Welcome.
I'm gonna clear these plates.
Let me. excuse me. let
me grab that from you.
- Thank you.
When was the last time
you saw her. your girl?
- I don't know you.
- Has it been days. weeks?
This is Frannie. Fran. my lady.
She wouldn't fall
prey to the reclaimed.
but she just
disappeared 10 days ago.
She was foraging in the area.
mentioned seeing a
house with power.
That's the last time I saw her.
In old times. if you
were gone for two weeks.
I mean. you're considered dead.
There's no question about it.
But now. with no
communication. you never know.
your person. they could
be out there for years.
And unfortunately. the
reality is sometimes
you're better off not
finding them at all.
(Emma screaming)
(glass shattering)
- [Mae] Hey. it's okay.
Let's get you into
the other room.
Come on.
- [Tom] You're gonna need
to eat something. my friend.
- [Mae] Hey.
- I just need to take a nap.
- Whoa. whoa. whoa. hey. hey.
Help me get him up.
Hey. hey.
- Okay.
Hey. Mae.
I will take that gun.
(brooding music)
This is a nice piece
of hardware. grandma.
- I'll take that back when
you're done. of course.
- But of course.
What did you do to him?
I promise you. I'm
not fucking around.
You do think I'm stupid.
- No.
I think you're sleepy.
- You did it.
You crazy bitch.
you did poison me.
- No. I sedated you.
Fun fact about Ativan.
- Yeah?
- It works way past
its expiration date.
but it does have
some side effects.
- Yeah. what's that?
- Headaches.
Ethan. Ethan.
Hey. hey. stay with me. okay?
Stay with me.
I'll be right back.
Fuck.
Ethan. it's okay. stay
calm. I'll be right there.
(anxiety-inducing music)
(door creaking)
- [The Fox] Tom.
Tom.
- [Mae] Coming. Ethan.
- Mae. run!
- I hope you don't mind.
we let ourselves in.
Grab the gun.
- It's insulin.
I'm a diabetic.
- Keep lying.
- [The Fox] Maybe
we should shoot him.
See how she reacts.
- Yeah. go ahead. see if I care.
He's just another sucker.
- [Tom] Wait. wait.
No.
We're gonna search
this entire house
and we're gonna find some
proof that Frannie was here.
And then we're gonna
fucking kill you.
You. let's go.
I'm gonna search every
room in this house.
Wolf. watch her.
She's a lot.
I'm telling you.
Ethan. she drugged us.
she killed our wives.
- You don't know that.
- Wake up. kid!
She's not who you think she is.
We just gotta find proof.
(anxiety-inducing music)
- [The Wolf] I'll make it quick
if you help speed this up.
- Where's the fun in that?
- That's my kind of girl.
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom] God dammit!
Next room!
- [The Fox] What's in the barn?
- Dirt.
- She's nervous.
- No. it's just my
resting bitch face.
- Let's see about that.
Keep an eye on her.
(suspenseful music)
- [Tom] Hey. this will go
a lot faster if you helped.
Is that yours?
- It was Emma's.
- [Tom] Sorry to
hear that. brother.
Let's go do something about it.
(suspenseful music)
(piano key playing)
- [Tom] Hey. I think
I found something.
Hey. Mae. you
wanna explain this?
What are these. kill trophies?
- [The Fox] Wait.
- Tom.
- What?
- Isn't that Frannie's?
(suspenseful music)
- [Mae] Hey. hey. Ethan.
Ethan. put the gun down.
- You killed Emma.
- No.
No. I didn't.
- Is she dead?
- [Mae] Ethan.
- [Ethan] Look at me.
Is she dead?
When?
- A long. long time ago.
(suspenseful music)
- Grab Wolf.
Let's finish this.
- How long have I had amnesia?
- You have amnesia?
That's very interesting. Mae.
Hey. kid. can you tell
me about your accident?
Did you break your arm?
You remember?
Can you tell me about it?
I'll take that.
What are we gonna find in there?
Is that where you put her?
My wife?
(suspenseful music)
You tell him or I will.
- Tell me what?
- [The Fox] Hey.
Wolf. what'd you find?
(suspenseful music)
- Am I sick?
- No. you're not.
You're not sick. Ethan.
You're dead.
(suspenseful music)
Hey.
- It's Hunter!
(explosion booming)
(dramatic music)
(creature growling)
- [Mae] Just try to breathe.
- [Tom] You said you wanted
your gun back. right?
Let's start with the bullets.
(gunshot booming)
(Tom screaming)
(dramatic music)
(somber music)
(Ethan vomiting)
- It's okay.
Don't worry. you won't remember.
(somber music)
Hey.
How'd you sleep?
- Good. I think.
- Do you remember me?
No.
Do you know who I am?
- A friend?
- We're running out of food.
I need to hunt. I
could use your help.
- [Ethan] Sure.
- Get dressed.
I'll meet you downstairs.
- Hey. where'd you go?
- Where'd I what?
- You gotta stay with me. okay?
Don't. just leave it.
- You should go.
Leave me.
- Never. you hear me?
Okay. just try to keep up.
(pensive music)
If there's anyone. just
let me do the talking.
Hello?
We come in peace.
- Says a gal with a gun.
- It's for protection.
- [Kai] Oh. I understand.
In fact. I got some
protection of my own.
Not that.
I was referring to the skilled.
tiny person with a pistol
pointed at your heads.
- Hi.
- [Kai] Why don't we start
with some introductions?
I'm Kai.
That's my home.
And that pretty darling
right there is Caroline.
I like to call her.
"Little Miss Never Miss."
- I'm Emma. and this is Ethan.
- [Kai] She always do
all the talking. Ethan?
- I can speak for myself.
- I'd say that too.
- We'd be grateful for
anything. for food. shelter.
Please.
- Where you coming from?
- We were in a crash.
- Either of you sick?
Prove it.
Take your clothes off.
That's my offer.
take it or leave it.
Pants too.
- Come on. man.
You happy?
- I don't know. what
do you think. Caroline?
- They look normal.
- [Kai] Normal.
Run in and tell mama bear
we have some company.
- [Caroline] Why are they naked?
- [Kai] You know why.
What's our motto?
- Trust. but verify.
that's right.
- [Caroline] 'Cause of
what happened to Bobby.
- [Kai] Run inside now.
You can get dressed.
Go ahead.
There are rules. you break
'em. you're gone. or worse.
- Understood.
- Good.
Let's get you kids fed.
- You okay?
(clock ticking)
(Caroline giggling)
- [Kai] Thank you. sweetheart.
I imagine you two are thirsty.
We have a well on the property.
it's not pretty. but it's safe.
Unless you like
something a bit stronger.
- No. thank you.
- Nice cabinet.
- Oh. yeah. we had a barn
collapse on the property.
You know. just the
usual decay and time.
I didn't want to let her go
so I dismantled and denailed
and before you know it.
I got a coffee table here
and shelves there.
I reclaimed it.
Kind of like what the
planet's doing to us.
if you believe what the
news says. which I don't.
"The Reclaimed."
I mean. for wood.
it makes sense.
you know. you repurpose
something that's lost.
but for people. nah.
Seems a bit defeatist.
- Maybe we deserve it.
I mean. look at what
we've done to this planet.
to each other.
- You're not a religious
person. are you Emma?
"Though He slay
me. I hope in Him"
It's Job. Chapter
13 from the Bible.
That's a dangerous
thing. you know.
thinking the worst about people.
especially in times like these.
- [Emma] Easy for you to say.
After the last couple weeks.
hope is in short supply.
- [Kai] You know. I'm
sure you two have seen
your share of horrible things.
but I can assure you.
you do not have the market
cornered on suffering.
Anyway. maybe this
thing. whatever it
is. is a wake up call.
put us back into our places.
Now. think about it. think
about the last 100 years.
50 years. what we're capable of.
Maybe this is forcing us to
get back to what matters.
what's simple. faith. the
land. the water. family.
- [Caroline] Papa. dinner soon.
- [Kai] Anyway. I'm sorry.
I get a little philosophical
when I drink.
All right. let's eat.
- Hey. hey. sit.
You're gonna spook the deer.
(threatening music)
Finally. got one.
(gun clicking)
- [Ethan] It's close. but
you got the heart wrong.
- Yeah. yeah.
I ran out of red markers.
- How many times?
- Ethan. it's complicated.
- I have time.
- No. you don't have time.
You need to feed.
(gunshot booming)
- You actually did it.
- Don't sound so surprised.
- Ethan!
(climatic music)
(flesh squelching)
- [Mae] Your body is changing
And when you feed.
it halts the process.
and then you remember.
- Please. no!
(gunshots booming)
- It's okay. it's okay.
Don't look. it's
okay. it's okay.
Ethan.
- [Mae] Stay with me.
(flies buzzing)
- Stop that starin'. Caroline.
- Yes. Papa.
- [Kai] Our guests are
starving. sweetheart.
Now. these are
real farm to table.
grown right outside in the back.
- It looks amazing. doesn't it?
- It sure does.
- It's the least we could do
after Caroline
pulled a gun on you.
- [Kai] Oh. we're well
past that. right. Caroline?
- Shall we say grace?
- Actually. maybe
I should wash up.
- Oh.
- [Sarah] Oh.
- Where are my manners?
Upstairs. second
door to the left.
- We'll be right back.
- Are you sure
they're okay. sweetie.
- Lord. these are
troubled times.
We've been led astray.
Now. more than ever. your
flock needs guidance.
Over to you sweetheart.
- [Caroline] Bless us. oh Lord.
for these gifts that
we are about to receive
from the bounty of
Christ. our Lord.
Amen.
- [Sarah] Amen.
- Amen.
- I can't do this.
- Yes. yes. you can.
I'm gonna buy us
some time. okay?
- Don't leave.
- Look at me.
Never. okay?
Hey. I'll be right back.
- Is everything okay?
- Oh. yeah. yeah.
Thank you again for
your hospitality.
- Of course.
- We're happy to.
- Sweetheart. why don't you to
take Caroline and go outside?
(distressing music)
- Kai.
- Sit down.
- Kai. maybe we should
talk about this.
- [Kai] Do it now. go on.
It's okay. sweetheart.
It's okay. love.
Put your filthy
hands on the table.
- Ethan needed to
use the restroom.
- [Kai] Where is your gun?
You know. I don't
know all the symptoms.
but that boy's lost.
He's soulless.
Doesn't even know his name.
He's got that amnesia.
- If maybe we could just-
- He don't look sick.
Just tired.
Is that how you fool
all your victims.
all the innocent people
like me and my family?
Is that what you do?
How long you been feeding him?
(distressing music)
- He's all I have left.
- Oh. you are the devil.
You are.
Does he even know what he is?
Does he?
See. you're just as infected
as he is. with weakness.
- Ethan.
Are you okay. dear?
(distressing music)
(Sarah screaming)
(exhilarating music)
(Emma screaming)
(gunshot booming)
(bleak music)
(Ethan yelling)
- Emma.
You're Emma.
How long have you
been doing this?
- Too long.
Look at me.
You have to eat daily. human
flesh and it can't be rotten.
I had to get creative
feeding you. which actually.
thanks to your amnesia.
wasn't that hard.
When you eat with regularity.
you are like the
fountain of youth.
But your memory's
inconsistent. unreliable.
Sometimes it returns right away.
and sometimes it takes longer.
It sounds horrible. I know.
but as long as I kept you clean
and fed. we were almost okay.
For a while. we had
a good thing going.
In a twisted way. it was
like time stood still.
a permanent honeymoon.
Then. weeks became years.
and one day. you
stopped recognizing me.
Good morning. lazy bones.
Hey.
- I'm sorry.
What?
- [Mae] Then. I started
the full-time charade.
You know. you caught
on a few times.
- Wait. are you Emma?
- [Mae] But as the years
passed. less and less.
- [Ethan] I'm a monster.
- No. you're the new normal.
I'm the one facing extinction.
- You should let me die.
- [Mae] That's the problem.
I did.
(solemn music)
My body is broken.
I'm broken.
I can't do this anymore.
- Me neither.
(solemn music)
(gunshot booming)
- [Mae] Ethan. stop.
(solemn music)
♪ Ah ♪
♪ And I don't hardly know her ♪
- Emma. I love you.
♪ Crimson and clover ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ When she come walking over ♪
♪ Now I've been
waitin' to show her ♪
♪ Crimson and clover ♪
♪ Over and over ♪
What are you doing?
- I'm letting go.
♪ Crimson and clover
over and over ♪
(solemn music)
(bright music)
(bright music continues)
(reflective music)
-== [ www.OpenSubtitles.org ] ==-